malwarefixes.com 2019-03-05

# Privacy Statement - MalwareFixes

This Policy describes the information that is collected in relation to your use of the Site (malwarefixes.com) and the Services, explains how Data is used and instances when Malwarefixes, collectively referred to as “malwarefixes.com or Malwarefixes”, shares or permits collection of the Data by the Company, as well as affiliates, partners and advertisers (hereinafter — “Partners”) of malwarefixes.com and the Company or state authorities. The Policy also provides explanation of the instruments you may use in order to limit the amount of Data collected by malwarefixes.com, the Company and/or Partners.

## 1\. Applicability and Acceptance of Policy

This Policy shall apply to your use of the Site and/or the Services as of the moment you first access the Site and commence use of any of the Services. By accessing, browsing or using the Site and/or any of the Services you irrevocably and unconditionally accept and adhere to provisions of this Policy without any exemptions, limitations and exclusions. For the avoidance of any doubts, this Policy shall apply to Services specifically identified in Terms. In the event you disagree with any provision of the Policy or would not like to provide your consent for collection of Data please cease use the Site or any of the Services immediately. You hereby acknowledge and agree that this Policy applies to any and all Data collected by or transmitted to malwarefixes.com, the Company and/or the Partners in the course of operation of the Site or provision of the Services, unless terms of service related to other products, utilities and offerings of malwarefixes.com, the Company and/or the Partners or use of the Site and/or the Services when you are logged in to the account provided by the Company contain specific prevailing provisions with this respect.

## 2\. Data Collected by malwarefixes.com, the Company and/or the Partners

Data collected hereunder in the course of operation of the Site and provision of the Services may differ depending on whether you access the Site and the Services logged in to your account provided by the Company as per Section 4 of the Terms or without logging in. In the event you are logged in to the account provided by the Company Data collected by the Company may be associated with our account by the Company. malwarefixes.com, the Company and Partners shall be entitled to combine Data collected in the course of your interaction with different sections of the Site or the Services with any other relevant available information. Data collected by or transmitted to malwarefixes.com, the Company or Partners, in the course of accessing, interaction and operation of the Site and provision of the Services may include, without limitation, the following Data: (i) Internet Protocol (IP) address and location; (ii) cookie information; (iii) browser identification information; (iv) information on your software and hardware; (v) date and time of accessing the Site and the Services; (vi) information of third parties websites referred the Site or the Services; (vii) information related to your activity in the course of the Services use, including, without limitation, search queries history, search results provided to you in response to your query, web pages you visited by reference from the search results; (viii) other information.

## 3\. Use of Data Collected by malwarefixes.com, the Company and/or Partners

Like many other companies, Malwarefixes uses “cookies” to remember user preferences and maximize performance of our website and services. Additionally, cookies help us to identify returning users so, for example, we don’t need to ask them to enter their email and password on every visit. Any personal information we collect with cookies is not shared with any outside parties. Please note the information gathered by cookies is necessary to provide certain subscription services. We cannot provide those services to users who do not give their consent to the data processing carried out through cookies or whose browsers are set to reject all cookies. As is common on the Internet, Malwarefixes maintains log files of the traffic that visits our sites. For example, our servers may automatically record the information you or your browser send when you visit a website. These log files may include information such as your requests, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your system.

## 4\. Advertising Policies

We utilize thrid party vendors such as Google to provide advertising on our site. These vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to our web site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager. You may also visit aboutads.info to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising.

## 5\. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act?

Yes. Malwarefixes complies with all the regulations of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of the United States of America. Malwarefixes does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn we have collected personal information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems.

## 6\. Amendments to the Policy

We may update this policy at any time by posting additions or modifications on this web page. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email or via a prominent notice on our website and where necessary we will seek the prior consent of our users.

## 7\. Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact the Malwarefixes by emailing [webmaster@malwarefixes.com](mailto:webmaster@malwarefixes.com).
